

Asad Rehman

Software Engineer

Passionate to gain a solid foundation in software engineering in a private corporate environment where my experience in analysis, design, implementation and testing of software systems would highly contribute to the company's industry projects' success; To provide excellent problem solving and interpersonal skills in facilitating individual and group peak performance.



X Asad98587@gmail.com



+923108504577



Islamabad, Pakistan

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer Logic Powered Solutions

06/2022 - currently working

Islamabad, Pakistan

Achievements/Tasks

- Working as dotnet developer
- Took part in order to restructuring their OBS system.

Software Engineer NetSol Technologies

04/2022 - 06/2022

Islamabad

Achievements/Tasks

Get training on their domain knowledge

Junior Software Developer i3 Consulting

06/2020 - 03/2022

Islamabad, Pakistan

Achievements/Tasks

- Working on different platforms according to projects.
- Work as Full stack with .net core mvc ,Angular, and .net core
- Integrate Python AI model in the flask for IoT based project
- Created website backend and frontend in Laravel and Customize website in WordPress.
- Worked in android studio development wih fetching data from api and integerate azure cognitive serives.
- My areas of responsibility were front-end and backend development; designing templates, and writing efficient SQL queries. I worked on ASP.NET Core APIs, Angular, Python and MSSQL database

Intern

Sparks Foundation

08/2021 - 09/2021 Part Time

Remote

Achievements/Tasks

- Internship in IOT and Computer Vision
- Develop Fault, mask and object detection system

SKILLS



CERTIFICATES

Single Page Web Applications with AngularJS (08/2020 - 10/2020)

AWS Foundation For Machine Learning (08/2021 - 10/2021)

Data Science Foundations - Level 1 (07/2020 - 08/2020)

Data Visualization Using Python (07/2020 - 08/2020)

Machine Learning with Python - Level 1 (07/2020 - 08/2020)

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Company Shifting plan Automation (09/2021 - 10/2021)

Mask Detection System (07/2021 - 07/2021)

Real Estate Web App (04/2021 - 06/2021)

Object Detection Home Automation (03/2021 - 06/2021)

Al based Finding Lost Child (11/2020 - 02/2021)

Speaker Recognition System via Voice (10/2019 - 12/2019)

Hotel Managment (03/2018 - 06/2018)

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Punjabi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Artificial Intelligence

Machine and deep Learning

IoT

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelancer

Fiver

01/2019 - 12/2020

Islamabad,Pakistan

Achievements/Tasks

- Designing and building the website front-end via website builder in Wordpress.
- Fixed Bugs.
- Designing and managing the website back-end including database integrate it with wordpress.
- Conducting website performance tests and Monitoring the performance of the live website.
- Troubleshooting content issues.

EDUCATION

Bachelor in Software Engineering Bahria University Islamabad

09/2017 - 07/2021

Islamabad,Pakistan

Fsc

IMCB f7/3

2014 - 2016

Islamabad,Pakistan